Dear Edward, I've gone back and forth the last few days trying to decide whether or not I should even write this.
亲爱的爱德华 这几日我一直在犹豫究竟该不该把我想说的写下来
In the end, I realized I would regret it if I didn't, so here goes.
最后我想 如果不写 我一定会后悔, 所以才有了这封信
I know the last time we saw each other, we weren't exactly hitting the sweetest notes.
记得你我最后一次相见, 可以说是不欢而散
It certainly wasn't the way I wanted the trip to end.
以如此的方式收场 当然不是我的本意
I suppose I'm responsible, and for that I'm sorry.
这事儿责任在我 在此我说声抱歉
But, in all honesty, if I had the chance, I'd do it again.
但说实话 如果再给我一次机会 我还是会做出相同的决定
Virginia said I left a stranger, and came back a husband.
维吉尼亚说 我走的时候像个陌生人, 回来时却成了她最爱的丈夫
I owe that to you.
关于这一点 我欠你的情
There's no way I can repay you for all you've done for me...
你为我做的一切 我无以回报
so rather than try, I'm just going to ask you to do something else for me.
既然如此 我索性直接开口 求你再为我做一件事
Find the joy in your life.
请你去寻找生命中的快乐
You once said you're not everyone.
你曾经说过 你并非普通人
Well, that's true.
这话是没错
You're certainly not everyone.
你当然不是普通人
But everyone is everyone.
但每个人都是普通人
My pastor always says:
我的牧师总说
"Our lives are streams...
"我们的生命就像小溪…
flowing into the same river...
最后汇入同一条大河…
towards whatever heaven lies in the mist beyond the falls."
大河尽头的瀑布之上 在迷雾后若隐若现的 就是天堂
- Hello, sweetie, Hi.
- 你好啊 宝贝， 嗨
Find the joy in your life, Edward.
寻找你生命中的快乐吧 爱德华